Shubham Sharma

Software Engineer

Frontend developer with 2+ years of experience building visually appealing websites using ReactJS, Redux, HTML-CSS, JavaScript. Experienced in working with Angular framework and have a strong understanding of GIT version control. Experienced in working in Agile environments, using Scrum to improve project workflows and increase efficiency.

\times	shubhr0813@gmail.com
•	7830797962
0	Raipur C.G
(E)	shubhsportfolio.netlify.app
in	linkedin.com/in/shubhs18
	github.com/shubhshar

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Tech Mahindra

08/2021 - 04/2023

Pune, India

 Built website components using ReactJS, Redux, JavaScript, ES6, HTML5, CSS3, Git, and Oracle SQL.
 Optimized website performance using a variety of performance optimization techniques and made the website responsive with a strong understanding of CSS-based design & cross-browser compatibility.

Software Engineer Trainee

ANR Software

03/2021 - 07/2021

Noida, India

 Successfully developed and deployed web applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, resulting in a 20% increase in user satisfaction. Integrated front-end and back-end aspects of web applications with a strong understanding of web standards.

EDUCATION

B. Tech (Computer Science)

Dr. APJ Abdul Kalam Technical University

07/2016 - 01/2021

7.2 GPA

SKILLS

ReactJS Redux Angular HTML CSS

Javascript Oracle SQL Bootstrap Git

PROJECTS

Onward Billing Portal (Client- British Telecom)

- Developed and deployed a React-based web application for different users that displayed data populated in database using a legacy application running on server.
- Technology used: React, Redux, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Oracle SQL, RestAPI, Java (Spring), Jenkins

Gaztec Rate Upload (Client- British Telecom)

- Developed the web pages according to design and integrated the APIs in the web application.
- Technology used: HTML/CSS, Angular, JavaScript, Spring, OracleSQL., Shell-Script.

Gaztec Network Mediation (Client- British Telecom)

- Developed lookups based on criteria provided by designer and deploy the jar on server and process the CDR accordingly.
- Technology Used: Java, SQL, Shell script, UNIX commands.

E-Restaurant management (Anr Software)

- Developed the responsive web pages according to the client requirements. Added responsiveness to the pages for seamless user experience.
- Technology used: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, OracleSQL.

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency